We now go live to our
eye-in-the-sky hovercopter
on the scene of that
terrible hovercopter crash.
Jim?
The news is not good.
I've just learned that my final
words were, "Back to you, Linda".
One for the blooper reel.
The news
is so violent.
Let's watch
Rachael Ray instead.
No, wait, there might be chopping.
God, what a wuss. Stop being
such a spineless jellyfish.
You know full well I am more
closely related to the sea cucumber.
Not where it counts.
I hated Jim!
In other news, our city's
filthy, urine-soaked walls
have been desecrated by a
mysterious tile-work graffiti artist.
Police have no leads
as to who's behind
this innovative
scourge of public art.
That is one sexy
bridge abutment.
Free corn? Well, that'll suit me just fine.
The key is knowing
precisely where to strike.
Oops.
Well, well. Time to
beat him his rights.
You know, that don't look
half bad on your buttocks.
It does sort of
class-up the place.
The time is 4:00 a.m.!
We've been arguing all night,
Kif. Can't we go to bed?
Is that all
you ever think about?
I'm not just some
piece of tofu, Amy.
I need to know where we stand
in our relationship.
We're just going
through a rough patch.
It is not a patch.
It's been ages,
according to your wildly inappropriate
hunk-of-the-month calendar.
Leave Todd out of this.
Thanks, babe. Also, today is
Canadian Independence Day.
That's Bender's ringtone.
I recognize the smell.
Hello?
Yo, Amy,
I'm in the slammer.
Oh, no.
That's enough lip
out of you, moneybags.
Just get 5 grand
and bail me out.
I don't have that kind of money laying around.
Yeah, you do. You know the floor
safe where you keep 10 grand?
There's 5 grand in there.
Don't make me wait.
Hey, Bender, you ever
kill a man with a sock?
It ain't so hard.
I'd better carve a shiv
for protection.
Rodriguez. These two brothers bailed your ass out.
Oh! Thank God.
Tell me, have things
changed on the outside?
Is food finally in pill form? What
about pills? Are they in food form?
Hey, hot stuff, I'm Larry,
the murder burglar.
Hi, Larry,
I like your tattoos.
Amy, that man
is a criminal.
I'm just checking out
his tats.
Sneato.
I have one of my mom.
Want to see?
Sure.
I just don't get why you have to
flirt with every bad boy in sight.
Quit exaggerating.
Nobody move or sweet cheeks here gets it.
Ooh!
You're bad.
Mama said,
"Spock you out".
That's it, Amy.
Pardon my language, but I have had
it with you ruffling my petticoats.
You and I are through!
Aw!
Here's a little song I wrote
to cheer you up. It's called...
Let's go already
Here's to Amy, single,
lonely and fabulous.
Thanks, everybody. Looks
like I'm back in the game.
Yeah,
the game of old maid.
Excuse me, sir,
are those yours?
You're damn right, and before
you ask, this is mine, too.
Tough break, Amy. Are you
and Kif getting divorced?
No. Technically, we were Fon-Fon-Rus,
so we weren't really married.
Wow, the interesting
thing about that is...
So, Amy, how can I
phrase this delicately?
Why did Kif dump you like a
sack of yesterday's turds?
He says I have a thing for
bad boys. It's so stupid.
The truth is
often stupid.
Bender, why do you have to
be so mean to me?
Shut up, baby,
you love it.
Don't tell me
to shut up.
You know what happened to the
last guy who told me to shut up?
What?
That was great.
Shut up.
Come over here.
Remember, love between a
human and a robot is taboo.
We can't tell anyone,
not even our co-workers.
Got it. I'll show
the utmost discretion
as we get nasty
in this glass tube.
I think I'm coming
down with circus-itis.
I thought circus-itis
only affected children.
Children of all ages.
Bender, old friend,
what's on your face?
Blood. You know,
shaving of the face beard.
Amy, are those gear imprints
on your sweatpants?
Uh, maybe. So what?
Well, I only brought it up
'cause Bender's wearing them.
Uh...
I stole them from her. Yeah,
that's it, call the cops.
Oh, my swollen feet.
I'd better take my pills.
Amy, I reckon sweet talk
don't come natural to me,
but of everyone
I've ever dated,
you are probably
in the top 10.
Aw.
You always say just the wrong
thing in just the right way.
Sinners! Robosexuality
is an abomination!
This guy.
The good book sayeth a robot
shall not lie down with a human,
nor do it standing up,
nor at any angle in between.
Hey, he's right.
I don't like this.
...in the good book.
Look, a single mother!
Let's get her!
Quickly,
into the ship's basement!
Now then, as you all know, the
county fair is approaching once again,
so I'm preparing my entry of
pickled winds and weathers.
I've got sunny, snow flurries, hail with onions,
even my grandmother's
cranberry-raisin typhoon,
but no tornado.
I'll be damned if I let Mrs.
Girdleson take the blue ribbon again.
That's why I need you folks to get
out there and harvest a nice ripe one.
This cattle prod
should help.
How will that...
Get out there!
Is everybody in position?
What?
Is someone talking?
Okay, good! On three!
One!
What did she say?
Two!
Wait, I'm not in position!
Three!
I'm ready for
the countdown!
I'm not hearing anyone!
Abort mission!
She said go!
Good work, everyone.
Honestly, that went
better than I expected.
I just need to reduce it
down into this pickle jar,
toss in a bay leaf to impress
those stupid judges.
Hey, where's
Amy and Bender?
They're missing out
on some hot pickle action.
Sounds like a muskrat's
caught in there.
That's Amy's sweatshirt.
And that's Bender's hat
from the Players' Ball!
Sweet tornados of Barbados! Amy
and Bender have been torn to shreds.
Oh, the humanity!
Also, Bender.
Uh-oh.
What's going on here?
Uh...
Nothing.
A pair of deviant robosexuals? Not under my roof.
What about on the roof?
Get your mind
out of the gutter!
What about in the gutter?
Professor, there's nothing
wrong with robosexuality.
Yeah, when the lights go
out, it's nobody's business
what goes on between
two consenting adults.
Or one.
Thanks, guys.
Everything will be okay as long
as my parents don't find out.
Mom? Dad?
Come home, Amy. It your
decision. We can't make you.
Attagirl.
Uh-oh.
Not the innocent whistling.
Repent!
This guy.
Look,
we're your family,
and if you can't talk
about your problem with us,
that would be great.
I don't have a problem!
I'm in a happy relationship that
just happens to be robosex...
You finish that word,
you kill your parents!
Low wine level detected.
Thank you.
Stop seducing him,
you hussy!
Dad!
I'm attracted to Bender, not
this emotionless wine bucket!
Hopes deleted.
Robotic brothers, the path to robot
hell is paved with human flesh!
Neat!
Over the course
of this
escape-proof workshop,
your software will be reprogrammed through prayer.
And by some tech-support guys in India.
But I read in Esqwired magazine that some robots
are hardwired
to be robosexual.
Don't believe
those lies, son!
The only lies worth believing
are the ones in the Bible.
Can I get a "Amen"?
I'll take a-three-men.
Holla!
Come on, Amy.
Pick a male human already.
I want to be a grandmother nine
months from five minutes from now.
Cut it out, Mom!
I'm not interested in any
of these gross, ugly losers!
What about this gross,
ugly, smelly loser?
Fry!
What you doing here?
I'm here to rescue Amy
from her robosexual desires.
If I understand
you correctly,
I've seen the error
of my ways?
Look at all that
awkward winking.
It must be love.
My parents may be evil,
but at least they're stupid.
In this phase, you will literally
wrestle with your demons.
Your shapely,
buxom, human demons.
Look at the rack on that one.
I mean, that one on the rack!
Good! That's real good.
Okay, everybody
switch demons.
No point in staying
with just one demon.
Now, work it hard!
Harder! Till the sin
explodes out of you!
Mmm.
Mercy. Okay,
the Lord's work is done.
Now, now, cuddle.
Cuddle with your demons.
Amy, I wonder where
you are right now.
I'm inside the dummy
to rescue you!
Well, that answers that.
Wait... Amy?
Bender, be careful!
Fry? Leela?
You're in there, too?
I guess we should
have waited in the ship.
Listen up, everybody,
I love Amy, and I'm tired
of pussyfootcupping around!
I finally found someone I want to
spend the rest of her life with.
Amy,
will you marry me?
Yes! Yes!
Oh, I'm just glad I didn't
live to see this day.
Hey, wait a second.
No!
So, it's a stone.
Is it real?
Hooray!
Hooray denied!
Need I remind you that
robosexual marriage is illegal?
Not in Space,
Massachusetts.
You mean
Space-tax-achusetts?
No chance, stretch pants! We're
gonna fight to legalize it right here!
Yeah, man!
You got to legalize it!
We're talking about
robosexual marriage.
We're talking
about lots of stuff.
Cool. Can you turn
into a race car?
Nah, I'm just
a pre-op transformer.
Thank you for coming,
everyone.
We're all having some good,
clean fun here.
Squeaky, squishy clean.
But it's time to discuss
a pressing issue,
the right to marry
who or what we want!
Yeah!
Legalize it!
Every other couple
has the right to marry.
Robot and fembot,
man and woman,
man and man.
Our poodle has two daddies.
Interracial,
interplanetary,
even ghost and horse,
but not robot and human!
That's why we're introducing
this ballot initiative
to legalize
robosexual marriage!
Yeah!
Legalize it!
If you hate intolerance and
being punched in the face by me,
please support
Proposition Infinity!
As election day nears, Prop Infinity
appears doomed to certain defeat.
Doomed!
More fair and
balanced coverage
after a word
from our sponsor,
No on Infinity.
A storm is gathering.
A storm of
robosexual marriage
that will rain down on us
like fire.
It's probably a firestorm.
If robosexual
marriage becomes legal,
imagine the horrible things
that will happen to our children,
then imagine
we said those things,
since we couldn't
think of any.
As a mother,
those things worry me.
Vote no on Infinity. Paid for
by the Farnsworth Foundation.
We can't compete against that
much stock footage of clouds!
We're boned!
But we still have one hope,
my big televised debate!
I'm our A in the hole!
Professor, who's debating
for your side?
That guy, you know,
I forget his name.
That's him!
Good evening. I'm George Takei's head and neck,
your host for tonight's debate. You may applaud.
We flipped a coin
before the debate,
and Bender stole it,
so we'll start with him.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury, I...
Oops. Sorry,
force of habit.
I support
this proposition
because I love a goopy,
flesh-and-blood woman,
and, not surprisingly,
she loves me.
This is a simple matter of
justice, which I'm not normally for.
So, please, vote yes.
After all, our love isn't
any different from yours,
except it's hotter,
'cause I'm involved.
I haven't heard
such an eloquent speech
since Bill Shatner explained
why he couldn't pay me back.
Rebuttal, Professor?
This $4 coffeepot
talks about love,
but what he describes
is perversion!
You wouldn't know perversion if
it put clamps on your testicles!
You're just jealous, 'cause
you've never known true love!
Oh, no? Back when I was full of
piss and vinegar, and my bed wasn't,
I fell in love with
the sweetest girl
ever to skip through
a field of posies.
Her name was Eunice,
and we spent our blissful days working in a lab,
developing a poison to wipe out
that dreadful posy infestation.
I thought our love
would last forever.
But then, 43 years later,
she left me
for a robot!
How could she do that
to me, her Farnypoo!
That's it?
You hate robosexuals
'cause your girlfriend
left you for a robot?
She didn't just leave me for
a robot, she was a robot!
Oh, God, her name wasn't Eunice, it was Unit!
Unit 47!
My heart was broken, and
like a bitter, old picklepuss,
I took it out on robosexuals
everywhere. I'm so ashamed!
At the risk of
losing this debate,
I beg you, support
Proposition Infinity!
Give me a hug!
I, too, am hugging them in spirit.
And now they're hugging me back. Oh, my.
In a stunning turnabout, voters
have approved Proposition Infinity.
Robosexual marriage
is now legal.
What's next,
gay robosexual marriage?
We did it, honey!
Finally, we can have
a legal, monogamous marriage,
like everyone else!
Yeah... Monogamous?
And now,
a long-distance dedication
from a squishy, green bad boy
to his pink pork dumpling.
At number 12,
it's Wailing Fungus with
Shut Up and Love Me.
Shut up and love me
I told you where
I told you when
I told you how
And we'll meet up at 10:00
But you keep on talking
Keep on yakking
Shut up and love me